Poughkeepsie Postcard and Flyer Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 3. Clubs/Homes/Societies, 1906-1930
  - Y.M.C.A., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1912-05-04 (Box 1, Folder 236)
  - Y.W.C.A. Building, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1920-06-08 (Box 1, Folder 237)
  - Y.W.C.A., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1913 (Box 1, Folder 238)
- 4. Hospitals, 1907-1944
  - Birdseye View of State Hospital, Poughkeepsie, N.Y. [Hudson River State Hospital], 1943-08-11 (Box 1, Folder 239)
  - Central Group Hudson River State Hospital. Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1909-02-10 (Box 1, Folder 240)
  - Central Group of Buildings, Hudson River State Hospital, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 241)
  - Chapel of Our Lady, H.R.S. Hospital, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 242)
  - Chapel of Our Lady, Hudson River State Hospital, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1909-12-12 (Box 1, Folder 243)
  - Conservatory, Hudson River State Hospital, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1912-07-03 (Box 1, Folder 244)
  - Conservatory, Hudson River State Hospital, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 245)
  - Conservatory, Hudson River State Hospital, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1912-09-01 (Box 1, Folder 246)
  - Entrance to Hudson River State Hospital, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 247)
  - Greenhouse, Hudson River State Hospital. Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1907-09 (Box 1, Folder 248)
  - Hudson River State Hospital, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 249)
  - Hudson River State Hospital, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1908-08-06 (Box 1, Folder 250)
  - Hudson River State Hospital, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 251)
  - Hudson River State Hospital, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 252)
  - Hudson River State Hospital, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 253)
  - Hudson River State Hospital, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 254)
  - Poughkeepsie, N.Y. Glimpse of Main Bldg. Hudson River State Hospital., 1911-04-24 (Box 1, Folder 255)
  - Road to Cottages, Hudson River State Hospital. Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1908-04-16 (Box 1, Folder 256)
  - Trolley Station, At Main Entrance, Hudson River State Hospital, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1935-05-09 (Box 1, Folder 257)
  - Walking Party, Hudson River State Hospital. Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1907-10-09 (Box 1, Folder 258)
  - St. Francis Hospital Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 259)
  - St. Francis Hospital Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 260)
  - Entrance. - Vassar Brothers Hospital, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 261)
  - Entrance, Vassar Hospital, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 262)
  - Vassar Bros. Hospital, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1944-08-24 (Box 1, Folder 263)
  - Vassar Bros. Hospital, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 264)
  - Vassar Bros. Hospital, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 265)
  - Vassar Hospital Entrance, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1921-06-16 (Box 1, Folder 266)
  - Vassar Hospital, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1915-08-11 (Box 1, Folder 267)
  - Vassar Hospital, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1907-10-17 (Box 1, Folder 268)
  - Vassar Hospital, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1907-07 (Box 1, Folder 269)
  - Vassar Hospital, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 270)
- 5. Civil War Memorials, 1907-1921
  - Cedar Creek Monument. 128th Regt. Monument, Pokeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Eastmans Memorial Fountain, 1908-06-05 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Memorial Fountain, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Memorial Fountain, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Memorial Fountain, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1915-12-09 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Memorial Fountain, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Memorial Fountain, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1921-08-13 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Soldier Fountain, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Soldier’s Fountain, Compliments of Poughkeepsie Chamber of Commerce, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Soldier Fountain, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Soldier Fountain, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1911-01-24 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Soldiers Memorial Fountain, Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Soldiers Memorial Fountain, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Soldiers Memorial Fountain, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Soldiers Memorial Fountain, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1907-01-06 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Soldiers Memorial Fountain, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Soldiers Memorial Fountain, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Soldiers Memorial Fountain, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1910-12-12 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Soldiers Memorial Fountain, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1907-03-06 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Soldiers Memorial Fountain, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1917-05-21 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Soldiers’ Monument, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1914-08-05 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- 6. Schools, 1905-1938
  - Columbus Institute, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1909-08-24 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Columbus Institute, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Eastman College and High School Building, Washington Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Eastman College and High School, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1907-12 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Eastman College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Eastman College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1912-09-23 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Eastman College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Eastman College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1914-02-06 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Eastman College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1908-05-02 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Eastman College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1907-10 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Eastman Terrace, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1915-09-10 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Glen Eden Seminary, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1915-07-27 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Glen Eden Seminary, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1912-10-30 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Lyndon Hall School. Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Lyndon Hall School. Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Pine Street School, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - High School, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - High School, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1929-08-31 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - High School, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1938-07-10 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - High School, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - High School, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - New High School, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Poughkeepsie High School Football Team, 1905., 1905-12-09 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Poughkeepsie High School, N.Y., 1905-10-06 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Putnam Hall School, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1908-11-20 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Putnam Hall School, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1906-02-16 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Putnam Hall School, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1907-08-08 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Putnam Hall School, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1907-11-25 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Poughkeepsie, N.Y. River View, Military Academy, 1909-11-06 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Riverview Academy, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1905-06-21 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Riverview Academy, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - River View, Military Academy, Otis Bisbee, Founder. Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1907-11-06 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - River View Military Academy, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - River View Military Academy, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1916-05-11 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Ungraded School, P.H.S., Eastman Park, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1915-07-12 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Ungraded School, P.H.S., Eastman Park, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1915-05-05 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- 7. Churches, 1905-1953
  - Christ Episcopal Church and Rectory, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Christ Episcopal Church and Rectory, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Christ Episcopal Church & Rectory, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1909-04-26 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Christ Episcopal Church, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Poughkeepsie, N.Y. Christ Episcopal Church., Undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Congregational Church, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1913-01-06 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - First Presbyterian Church, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1909-10-11 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - First Presbyterian Church, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1953-05-20 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Old Dutch Reformed Church, Town Clock, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1905-08-20 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Old Dutch Reformed Church, Town Clock, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Reformed Church, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Second Dutch Reformed Church, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Poughkeepsie, N.Y. St. Mary’s Catholic Church, 1909-08-24 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - St. Mary Catholic Church, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1913-12-08 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - St. Mary’s Church, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1909-10-06 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - St. Mary’s Church, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - St. Mary’s Church, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1920-08-22 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - St. Mary’s Church, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1934-02-23 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - St. Peter’s Catholic Church and Rectory. Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Trinity Methodist Church, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Trinity Methodist Church, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 78)
- 8. Streets, 1906-1921
  - Academy Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Academy Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1910-03-11 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Church Street from Academy Street, looking East, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1912-06-30 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Hyde Park Road, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Corner Main and Market Streets, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Main St. from Academy St., Looking East, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1912-09-15 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Main St., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Market St., 1911-08-25 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Main Street, East from Garden Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1921-11-08 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Main Street from Academy Street, Looking West, At Night, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1917-08-12 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Main Street, from Market Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1911-08-29 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Main Street, from Morgan House, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1916-08-06 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Main Street looking East Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Main Street, Looking East, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1918-03-09 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Main Street looking West, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1911-06-03 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Main Street, Poughkeepsie, Undated (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Main Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Main Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1909-10-18 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Main Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Main Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Main Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., illuminated for Firemen’s Convention, 1909., Undated (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Main Street with Morgan House, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Poughkeepsie, N.Y. Main Street showing Morgan House, 1910-09-12 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Court of Honor, Firemen’s Convention, 1909, Po’keepsie, N.Y. [Market Street], Undated (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Court of Honor, Market Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., decorated for Firemen’s Convention, 1909., Undated (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Court of Honor, Market Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., illuminated for Firemen’s Convention, 1909., Undated (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Market Street looking North, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1913-07-11 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Market Street, Looking South, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Market Street, Looking Toward Main. Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Market Street, North from Nelson House, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Market Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Market Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Market Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1906-05-01 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Market Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1906-04-17 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Market Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y. Smith Brothers Restaurant, Nelson House and Post Office, Undated (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Market Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y. Smith Brothers Restaurant, Nelson House & Post Office., Undated (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Mill Street looking East Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1908-06-03 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Montgomery Street, East from Market St., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1909-02-23 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - South Road, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Washington Street from Main Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Washington Street from Main, looking North, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Washington Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1908-01-23 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Washington Street showing Columbus Hall, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 120)
- 9. Bridges/ Boats/ The Hudson River, 1905-1931
  - Ayrults Bridge, Wappingers Creek, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1909-05-11 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Boat Race Day at Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1912-12-17 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - The Docks and Hendrick Hudson Day Boat, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Hendrick Hudson under Poughkeepsie Bridge, N.Y., 1907-08-27 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Steamer “Hendrick Hudson” and Poughkeepsie Bridge, Hudson River, Undated (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - The Hudson River, Undated (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Mid-Hudson Bridge Highland, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Mid-Hudson Bridge, Highland-Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Mid Hudson Bridge, Highland-Poughkeepsie, N.Y. Showing Railroad Bridge, Undated (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Mid-Hudson Traffic Bridge, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Mid-Hudson Traffic Bridge, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Leading to Roosevelt Memorial Library and Home, Undated (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - New Hudson River Bridge. Poughkeepsie, N.Y. [Mid Hudson Bridge], Undated (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - New Hudson River Bridge. Poughkeepsie, N.Y. [Mid Hudson Bridge], 1931-08-06 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Along the Hudson River. The Bridge at Poughkeepsie, N.Y. [Poughkeepsie Bridge], Undated (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - The Poughkeepsie Bridge, 1906-09 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Poughkeepsie Bridge, 212 Feet High, Hudson River, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Poughkeepsie Bridge, Across the Hudson River, Undated (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - Poughkeepsie Bridge and Hudson River Day Boats, Undated (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Poughkeepsie Bridge. Compliments of Poughkeepsie Chamber of Commerce., Undated (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - The Poughkeepsie Bridge, Highland, N.Y., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - Poughkeepsie Bridge on the Hudson River, 1909-07-28 (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Poughkeepsie Bridge Over Hudson River, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - Poughkeepsie Bridge, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - Poughkeepsie Bridge, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1909-09-03 (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - Poughkeepsie Bridge, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - Poughkeepsie Bridge, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1905-09 (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - Poughkeepsie Bridge, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1908-09-30-1908-09-31 (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - Poughkeepsie Bridge, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - Poughkeepsie Bridge, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1908-10-02 (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - Poughkeepsie, N.Y. Poughkeepsie Bridge. View from Highland Station, opposite Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1912-08-15 (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - S.S. “Albany” at Main Street Landing, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1912-08-13 (Box 2, Folder 151)
- 10. Parks, 1907-1943
  - College Hill Building, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1914-08-06 (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - College Hill House, College Hill Park, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1911-06-13 (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - College Hill Park, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - College Hill Park, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1907-11-09 (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - College Hill, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1909-05-27 (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - College Hill, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - College Hill, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - Conservatory, College Hill Park, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1910-08-22 (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - Dudley Memorial, College Hill Park, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1943-08-11 (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - Dudley Shelter: College Hill, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - Poughkeepsie, N.Y. College Hill Park, Undated (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - View from College Hill, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - Eastman Park, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1912-06-21 (Box 2, Folder 164)
  - Eastman Park, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - Eastman Park, View at Main Entrance, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 166)
  - Entrance to Eastman Park, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 167)
  - Entrance to Eastman Park, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 168)
  - Eastonian Park- South Entrance, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 169)
  - Madison Square Park, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1919-11-29 (Box 2, Folder 170)
  - Pelton Park, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 171)
  - The Lake- “Woodcliff Park,” Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 172)
- 11. Fire Companies, 1909
  - Apparatus of Cataract Steamer Co. No. 4, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 173)
  - Apparatus of Davy Crockett H. & L. Co., No. 1, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 174)
  - Crockett Fire House and Municipal Building illuminated for Firemen’s Convention, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1909 [Davy Crockett H. & L. Co], Undated (Box 2, Folder 175)
  - Davy Crockett, H. & L. Co., No. 1, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., August 1909 (Box 2, Folder 176)
  - Duty Apparatus of Davy Crockett H. & L. Co. No. 1, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 177)
  - Pig Supper. You are invited to attend the annual Pig Roast of Davy Crockett Hook and Ladder Co., at the Truck House on Saturday evening, December 31. Concert from 8 to 10 p.m. Roast from 10 to 12 p.m. O.C. Reichardt, E.J. Wolff, E. Bauer, House Committee., Undated (Box 2, Folder 178)
  - Apparatus of Lady Washington Hose Co. No. 3, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 179)
  - Apparatus of Niagara Steamer Co., No. 2, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 180)
  - Apparatus of O.H. Booth Hose Co., No. 2, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 181)
  - Apparatus of Phoenix Hose Co., No. 1, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 182)
  - Apparatus of Young America Hose Co., No. 6, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 183)
- 12. General Poughkeepsie, 1906-1916
  - the Day we celebrate, 8th Annual Encampment United Spanish War Veterans Dept. of New York Poughkeepsie, July 3-4-5, 1911, Undated (Box 2, Folder 184)
  - Compliments of Poughkeepsie Eagle. Dutchess County Agricultural Fair., 1910-10-18 (Box 2, Folder 185)
  - Souvenir of the Dutchess County Fair, 1908. Compliments of the Poughkeepsie Eagle., Undated (Box 2, Folder 186)
  - [Great Council Wigwam Convention], 1906-08-14 (Box 2, Folder 187)
  - Red Mens Convention Pokeepsie, N.Y. Aug 14-17, 1906 Souvenir Card- [Great Council Wigwam], Undated (Box 2, Folder 188)
  - Just A Greeting from Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 189)
  - Lover’s Lane, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1908-08-20 (Box 2, Folder 190)
  - Marist College, [Statue] “In Memory of the Deceased Parents and Benefactors of the Marist Brothers”, Undated (Box 2, Folder 191)
  - “Neutral in Nothing” – Poughkeepsie Journal 1785, Dutchess Intelligence 1828, Dutchess Republican 1831, Weekly Eagle 1834, Weekly Eagle changed to Semi-Weekly 1889, Daily Eagle first issued December 4, 1860, Undated (Box 2, Folder 192)
  - Start of Race, Parker in F.I.A.T. Racer. - Poughkeepsie N.Y. Ely in Curtiss Aeroplane. – Sept. 28, 1910, Undated (Box 2, Folder 193)
  - Birds Eye View looking West from Court House. Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 194)
  - Birds Eye View Looking West from Court House, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1908-05-28 (Box 2, Folder 195)
  - General View, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 196)
  - General View, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1916-05-28 (Box 2, Folder 197)
  - View on Wappingers Creek, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1910-09-03 (Box 2, Folder 198)
- 13. Business Advertisements, 1888-1889, Undated
  - Edwin Thorne, Putnam Nail Advertisement, Undated (Box 2, Folder 199)
  - Estey Piano Co. New York, Manufacturers., Undated (Box 2, Folder 200)
  - [Hands Holding One Another]. Compliments of Fred V. Waite, the Leading Picture Frame Manufacturer and Toy Dealer, 273 Main St., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 201)
  - Tan “oo” Tetch. Compliments of Fred V. Waite, the Leading Picture Frame Manufacturer and Toy Dealer, 273 Main St., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1889 (Box 2, Folder 202)
  - Use A & P Baking Powder. The G.T. Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co., Undated (Box 2, Folder 203)
  - Compliments of: Herrick The Furniture Man, Also Bedding, baby Carriages and Refrigerators, 395 Main Stree, Po’keepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 204)
  - J.T. Rider, Pianos and Organs, Compliments of A.L. Rider, Manager, Undated (Box 2, Folder 205)
  - J.T. Rider, Pianos and Organs, Compliments of A.L. Rider, Manager, Undated (Box 2, Folder 206)
  - J.T. Rider, Pianos and Organs, Compliments of A.L. Rider, Manager, Undated (Box 2, Folder 207)
  - J.T. Rider, Pianos and Organs, Compliments of A.L. Rider, Manager, Undated (Box 2, Folder 208)
  - [Portrait]. Joseph H. Zahn, Jr., Dealer in Elegant Stationary, School Books, Games, Novelties, Sporting Goods, Libraries, Magazines, and Newspapers, 156 Main St., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 209)
  - Luckey, Platt & Co., Dry Goods and Carpets, Poughkeepsie, N.Y. Clark’s O.N.T. Spool Cotton Trademark, Undated (Box 2, Folder 210)
  - Compliments of M. Shwartz, One Price Clothier, 303 to 307 Main Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 211)
  - A Sweet tooth. O.S. Atkins Down Town Dry Goods Store 149 and 151 Main Street Poughkeepsie, Undated (Box 2, Folder 212)
  - O.S. Atkins, Down Town Dry Goods Store 149 & 151 Main Street, Poughkeepsie., Undated (Box 2, Folder 213)
  - O.S. Atkins, Down Town Dry Goods Store 149 & 151 Main Street, Poughkeepsie., Undated (Box 2, Folder 214)
  - Quintard Brothers, 316 Main St., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 215)
  - Sampson Bros. Superior Made Clothing 302 and 304 Main St. Poughkeepsie, Undated (Box 2, Folder 216)
  - V. Schoonmaker, Manufacturer of all kinds of Carriages and Sleighs., Undated (Box 2, Folder 217)
  - Wheeler & Wilson New “No. 9”, 1888 (Box 2, Folder 218)